# **Kevin Quiveors**

Highly competent degreed drafting and design professional with over 22 years experience in the utility, civil and railroad industries.

Burlington, NJ - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Kevin-Quiveors/c2465d4513f538bc

Highly competent degreed drafting and design professional with over 22 years experience in the utility, civil and railroad industries. Adept in AutoCAD 2008 Civil 3D, Land Development Desktop and associated applications, and MicroStation J. Experience includes project management, training, safety, fieldwork and some minor survey. CompTIA A+ certified. Excellent organizational, interpersonal and written skills.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

# **CAD/Designer**

Consulting Engineer Services - Sewell, NJ - October 2010 to Present

Creation of Conceptual Plans, Land Development and Construction Packages. Support of Civil Engineers in commercial and residential sites using AutoCAD 2006, Land Development Desktop, Cooper Photometric Toolbox 32, Gardco Footprints and AutoTurn 7.0. Surface generation and Cut & Fill Analysis. Creation of Storm Water and Sewer Profiles. Night time lighting studies. Site Calculations (bulk requirements). Site analysis (photographs, comparison of plans to site for accuracy, measurements, locate utilities and structures).

# Senior CAD/Designer

Perks Division of Dresdner Robin - Pennsauken, NJ - November 2007 to June 2010

Creation of Conceptual Plans, Land Development and Construction Packages. Support of Civil Engineers in commercial and residential sites using AutoCAD Civil 3D 2008. Surface generation and Cut & Fill Analysis. Creation of Storm Water and Sewer Profiles. Site Calculations (bulk requirements). Site Analysis (photographs, comparison of plans to site for accuracy, measurements, locate utilities and structures). Importing of survey points to create point groups, manipulate and generate surfaces and create base plans. Survey instrument man.

## CAD/Designer

Consulting Engineer Services - Sewell, NJ - July 2006 to October 2007

Creation of Conceptual Plans, Land Development and Construction Packages. Support of Civil Engineers in commercial and residential sites using AutoCAD 2006, Land Development Desktop, Cooper Photometric Toolbox 32, Gardco Footprints and AutoTurn 7.0. Surface generation and Cut & Fill Analysis. Creation of Storm Water and Sewer Profiles. Night time lighting studies. Site Calculations (bulk requirements). Site analysis (photographs, comparison of plans to site for accuracy, measurements, locate utilities and structures).

# CAD/Designer

Bohler Engineering, Inc - Chalfont, PA - 2003 to 2006

Created Conceptual, Land Development and Construction Packages. Created Storm Water and Sewer Profiles and Roadway Cross-Sections. Supported Civil Engineers in multiple commercial and residential sites using AutoCAD 2000 & 2004, AutoTurn 5, and Land Development Desktop. Site Calculations (pervious and impervious coverage areas, drainage area calculations, parking calculations, etc.).

## **Draftsman**

Garg Consulting Services, Inc - Cherry Hill, NJ - 1999 to 2003

Supported Civil Engineers, Track Designers and Construction Personnel on the Hudson-Bergen Light Rail Transit System and the Meadows Maintenance Complex Project-124. Generated roadway and railroad cross-sections and according to current and future designs using MicroStation and AutoCAD. Helped create and maintain the arrangement of CAD files within the computer network. Created and compiled any necessary design files needed for bid packages. Aided in several Bridge Inspections in Northern New Jersey for the purpose of structural integrity.

144 Crossings Way

Lindenwold, NJ 08021-6195

Phone: (856) 627-9441 Cell: (267) 304-5661 E-mail: kevin.quiveors@gmail.com

### **Electric Facilities Drafter**

PECO Energy Company - Philadelphia, PA - 1987 to 1998

Supported the electrical distribution and transmission professionals as well as technical and craft personnel servicing southeastern Pennsylvania and northern Maryland. Provided drafting support to engineering and construction vendors and contractors. Maintained distribution and transmission design files for entire service area. Oversaw the development and management of large-scale conversions within the Philadelphia service area. Provided support during Storm Restoration by identifying transmission problems in the field, and interacted with PECO Energy customers face to face. Interfaced with construction foreman, PJM dispatcher and customer support personnel. Trained junior draftsmen in MicroStation, Passport, Customer Information Systems and the Nodes System. Designed instruction manuals for the Nodes System.

### **EDUCATION**

Camden County College 2010

# Associate of Arts in Computer Aided Drafting Technology

Lamar University 1987

## ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Highly competent degreed drafting and design professional with over 22 years experience in the utility, civil and railroad industries. Adept in AutoCAD 2008 Civil 3D, Land Development Desktop and associated applications, and MicroStation J. Experience includes project management, training, safety, fieldwork and some minor survey. CompTIA A+ certified. Excellent organizational, interpersonal and written skills.

#### AREAS OF EXPERTISE

Auto 2008 Civil 3D, AutoCAD 2006, Land Development Desktop, AutoTurn 5, Microstation J, Cooper Photometric Toolbox 32, Gardco Footprints, Internet Capabilities, Microsoft Office Suite, Passport, Trouble Management System, Customer Information System, Storm Restoration System (Screening), Nodes System